Guide to the The Exit Art Archive 1982 - 2011 MSS 343
© 2012 Fales Library and Special Collections
- Series I: Exhibition Files
  - Other America [2005.01]: Artist File - Minshik Shin (Box 116, Folder 2)
  - Other America [2005.01]: Artist File - Kiriko Shirobayashi (Box 116, Folder 3)
  - Other America [2005.01]: Artist File - Veronique Simar (Box 116, Folder 4)
  - Other America [2005.01]: Artist File - Jonathan Skurnik, 2004, 2005 (Box 116, Folder 5)
  - Other America [2005.01]: Artist File - Randy Stulberg (Box 116, Folder 6)
  - Other America [2005.01]: Artist File - Alison Elizabeth Taylor (Box 116, Folder 7)
  - Other America [2005.01]: Artist File - The 62 (Box 116, Folder 8)
  - Other America [2005.01]: Artist File - The 62, Liability Release Forms [1 of 2], March 2005 (Box 116, Folder 9)
  - Other America [2005.01]: Artist File - The 62, Liability Release Forms [2 of 2], March - April 2005 (Box 116, Folder 10)
  - Other America [2005.01]: Artist File - Lex Thompson (Box 116, Folder 11)
  - Other America [2005.01]: Artist File - Jennifer Trausch (Box 116, Folder 12)
  - Other America [2005.01]: Artist File - Brian Ulrich, 2004, 2005 (Box 116, Folder 13)
  - Other America [2005.01]: Loan Information (Box 116, Folder 14)
  - Other America [2005.01]: Shipping Correspondence (Box 116, Folder 15)
  - Other America [2005.01]: Exhibition Checklist, March 5, 2005 (Box 116, Folder 16)
  - Other America [2005.01]: Price List, March 5, 2005 (Box 116, Folder 17)
  - Other America [2005.01]: Wall Text/Signs, March 5, 2005 (Box 116, Folder 18)
  - Other America [2005.01]: Exhibition Preparation/Installation Information, December 2004 (Box 116, Folder 19)
  - Other America [2005.01]: Public Programs - Video Programs (Box 116, Folder 20)
  - Other America [2005.01]: Correspondence - Press, February - March 2005 (Box 116, Folder 21)
  - Other America [2005.01]: Press Clippings/Listings (Box 116, Folder 22)
  - prayingproject [2005.02]: Research, 2004 - 2005 (Box 117, Folder 1)
  - prayingproject [2005.02]: Call For Proposals, Narrative, April 15, 2005 (Box 117, Folder 2)
  - prayingproject [2005.02]: Press Release (Box 117, Folder 3)
  - prayingproject [2005.02]: Artist Sign-In Sheets, October - November 2004 (Box 117, Folder 4)
  - prayingproject [2005.02]: Invitations, March 2005 (Box 117, Folder 5)
  - prayingproject [2005.02]: Press Kit, April 15, 2005 (Box 117, Folder 6)
  - prayingproject [2005.02]: Brochure, April 15, 2005 (Box 117, Folder 7)
  - prayingproject [2005.02]: Schedule, April 15 - 17, 2005 (Box 117, Folder 8)
  - prayingproject [2005.02]: Correspondence, 2004 - 2005 (Box 117, Folder 9)
  - prayingproject [2005.02]: Publicity/Advertising (Box 117, Folder 10)
  - prayingproject [2005.02]: Artist Projects and Biographies, April 15, 2005 (Box 117, Folder 11)
  - prayingproject [2005.02]: Artist File - Rob Andrews (Box 117, Folder 12)
  - prayingproject [2005.02]: Artist File - Sarah Chokyi Bauer (Box 117, Folder 13)
  - prayingproject [2005.02]: Artist File - Paul Benney (Box 117, Folder 14)
  - prayingproject [2005.02]: Artist File - Maria Bussman, February 12, 2005 (Box 117, Folder 15)
  - prayingproject [2005.02]: Artist File - caraballo-farman (Box 117, Folder 16)
  - prayingproject [2005.02]: Artist File - Karen Dolmanisth (Box 117, Folder 17)
  - prayingproject [2005.02]: Artist File - Cecile Evans, February 15, 2005 (Box 117, Folder 18)
  - prayingproject [2005.02]: Artist File - Mayumi Ishino (Box 117, Folder 19)
  - prayingproject [2005.02]: Artist File - Berioska Ipinza (Box 117, Folder 20)
  - prayingproject [2005.02]: Artist File - Jae Rhim Lee (Box 117, Folder 21)
  - prayingproject [2005.02]: Artist File - Annie Murdock (Box 117, Folder 22)
  - prayingproject [2005.02]: Artist File - Nico and Katiushka (Box 117, Folder 23)
  - prayingproject [2005.02]: Artist File - Laura Nova (Box 117, Folder 24)
  - prayingproject [2005.02]: Artist File - Yashira Nun (Box 117, Folder 25)
  - prayingproject [2005.02]: Artist File - Praxis (Box 117, Folder 26)
  - prayingproject [2005.02]: Artist File - Pasha Baned Radetzki (Pasha Ra) (Box 117, Folder 27)
  - prayingproject [2005.02]: Artist File - Chemi Rosado-Seijo (Box 117, Folder 28)
  - prayingproject [2005.02]: Artist File - Akiko Sasamoto and Jeffrey Schiff (Box 117, Folder 29)
  - prayingproject [2005.02]: Artist File - Mark Stafford (Box 117, Folder 30)
  - prayingproject [2005.02]: Artist File - Riva Weinstein (Box 117, Folder 31)
  - prayingproject [2005.02]: Artist File - Beatrice L. Wolert (Box 117, Folder 32)
  - prayingproject [2005.02]: Concept - Accepted Proposals (Box 117, Folder 33)
  - Homomuseum [2005.03]: Research - Articles, 2003 (Box 117, Folder 34)
  - Homomuseum [2005.03]: Research - Artists (Box 117, Folder 35)
  - Homomuseum [2005.03]: Research - Exhibition/Events, 2001 - 2005 (Box 118, Folder 1)
  - Homomuseum [2005.03]: Research - Public Culture [1 of 3], undated, 2001 - 2005 (Box 118, Folder 2)
    This folder includes magazine, The Male Figure Volume 22.
  - Homomuseum [2005.03]: Research - Public Culture [2 of 3], 2001 - 2005 (Box 118, Folder 3)
  - Homomuseum [2005.03]: Research - Public Culture [3 of 3], 1990, 1995, 2002 - 2005 (Box 118, Folder 4)
    This folder includes the following:
    Dispatch #6. The Tom of Finland Foundation: Los Angeles, CA. Winter 2002.
    My Comrade. Les Simpson: New York, NY. Spring 1990.
    Plotz: The Zine for the Vaclempt. JewGirl Productions: New York, NY. 1995.
    Steam: A Quarterly Journal For Men. Volume 3, Issue 3. PDA Press: San Francisco, CA. Autumn 1995.
  - Homomuseum [2005.03]: Research - Organizations, 2002 - 2005 (Box 118, Folder 5)
  - Homomuseum [2005.03]: Funding - Research, 2002 (Box 118, Folder 6)
  - Homomuseum [2005.03]: Funding - Astraea Foundation, November 26, 2002 (Box 118, Folder 7)
  - Homomuseum [2005.03]: Funding - Emily Hall Tremaine Foundation, 2002 (Box 119, Folder 1)
  - Homomuseum [2005.03]: Call For Proposals, June 2004 (Box 119, Folder 2)
  - Homomuseum [2005.03]: Accepted Proposals (Box 119, Folder 3)
  - Homomuseum [2005.03]: Invitations, April 2005 (Box 119, Folder 4)
  - Homomuseum [2005.03]: Press Release, May 21, 2005 (Box 119, Folder 5)
  - Homomuseum [2005.03]: Correspondence - General (Box 119, Folder 6)
  - Homomuseum [2005.03]: Artist Contact List, undated (Box 119, Folder 7)
  - Homomuseum [2005.03]: Artist File - Christopher Arabadjis (Box 119, Folder 8)
  - Homomuseum [2005.03]: Artist File - Alvin Baltrop (Box 119, Folder 9)
  - Homomuseum [2005.03]: Artist File - James Bidgood (Box 119, Folder 10)
  - Homomuseum [2005.03]: Artist File - A.K. Burns (Box 119, Folder 11)
  - Homomuseum [2005.03]: Artist File - Christopher Clary (Box 119, Folder 12)
  - Homomuseum [2005.03]: Artist File - J.P. Forrest (Box 119, Folder 13)
  - Homomuseum [2005.03]: Artist File - Leor Grady (Box 119, Folder 14)
  - Homomuseum [2005.03]: Artist File - Blake Goble and Robert Ransick (Box 119, Folder 15)
  - Homomuseum [2005.03]: Artist File - Stephanie Gray (Box 119, Folder 16)
  - Homomuseum [2005.03]: Artist File - Stephanie Griffo (Box 119, Folder 17)
  - Homomuseum [2005.03]: Artist File - Geoffrey Hendricks and Sur Rodney (Sur) (Box 119, Folder 18)
  - Homomuseum [2005.03]: Artist File - Derek Jackson (Box 119, Folder 19)
  - Homomuseum [2005.03]: Artist File - Aaron Krach (Box 119, Folder 20)
  - Homomuseum [2005.03]: Artist File - Marget Long (Box 119, Folder 21)
  - Homomuseum [2005.03]: Artist File - Gabriel Martinez (Box 119, Folder 22)
  - Homomuseum [2005.03]: Artist File - J. Morrison (Box 119, Folder 23)
  - Homomuseum [2005.03]: Artist File - Rune Olsen (Box 119, Folder 24)
  - Homomuseum [2005.03]: Artist File - Predrag Pajdic and Rachel Wilberforce (Box 119, Folder 25)
  - Homomuseum [2005.03]: Artist File - Matthew Ravenstahl (Box 119, Folder 26)
  - Homomuseum [2005.03]: Artist File - Milton Rosa-Ortiz (Box 119, Folder 27)
  - Homomuseum [2005.03]: Artist File - Shane Ruth (Box 119, Folder 28)
  - Homomuseum [2005.03]: Artist File - Mary Ellyn Strom (Box 119, Folder 29)
  - Homomuseum [2005.03]: Artist File - Jonathan Wahl (Box 119, Folder 30)
  - Homomuseum [2005.03]: Artist File - Phillip Ward (Box 119, Folder 31)
  - Homomuseum [2005.03]: Loan Information (Box 119, Folder 32)
  - Homomuseum [2005.03]: Shipping Information, May 2005 (Box 119, Folder 33)
  - Homomuseum [2005.03]: Exhibition Checklist, May 21, 2005 (Box 119, Folder 34)
  - Homomuseum [2005.03]: Price List, May 21, 2005 (Box 119, Folder 35)
  - Homomuseum [2005.03]: Wall Labels, undated (Box 119, Folder 36)
  - Homomuseum [2005.03]: Narrative, undated (Box 119, Folder 37)
  - Homomuseum [2005.03]: Exhibition Preparation/Installation Information, February 2005 (Box 120, Folder 1)
  - Homomuseum [2005.03]: Archive Project, May 2005 (Box 120, Folder 2)
  - Homomuseum [2005.03]: Opening, undated (Box 120, Folder 3)
  - Homomuseum [2005.03]: Public Programs - Research (Box 120, Folder 4)
  - Homomuseum [2005.03]: Public Programs - Video Program, June 2005 (Box 120, Folder 5)
  - Homomuseum [2005.03]: Exhibition Tours, June 2005 (Box 120, Folder 6)
  - Homomuseum [2005.03]: Receipts, June 2005 (Box 120, Folder 7)
  - Homomuseum [2005.03]: Correspondence - Press, June 2005 (Box 120, Folder 8)
  - Homomuseum [2005.03]: Press Clippings, May 2005 (Box 120, Folder 9)
  - Traffic [2005.04]: Press Release, October 1, 2005 (Box 120, Folder 10)
  - Traffic [2005.04]: Exhibition Checklists, Artist Projects and Biographies, October 1, 2005 (Box 120, Folder 11)
  - Traffic [2005.04]: Research - Statistics, 2003, 2005 (Box 120, Folder 12)
  - Traffic [2005.04]: Research - NYC Bicycles (Box 120, Folder 13)
  - Traffic [2005.04]: Wall Text and Labels (Box 120, Folder 14)
  - Traffic [2005.04]: Loan/Release Forms (Box 120, Folder 15)
  - Traffic [2005.04]: Correspondence - Press (Box 120, Folder 16)
  - Traffic [2005.04]: Public Programs, September - October 2005 (Box 120, Folder 17)
  - Traffic [2005.04]: Shipping Invoices, October 2005 (Box 120, Folder 18)
  - Traffic [2005.04]: Tours (Box 120, Folder 19)
  - Traffic [2005.04]: Installation Instructions (Box 120, Folder 20)
  - Traffic [2005.04]: Invitations (Box 120, Folder 21)
  - Traffic [2005.04]: Correspondence - Publicity and Collaboration (Box 120, Folder 22)
  - Traffic [2005.04]: Arist File - Chantal Akerman, July 21, 2004 (Box 121, Folder 1)
  - Traffic [2005.04]: Artist File - Black Label Bicycle Club (Carlson) (Box 121, Folder 2)
  - Traffic [2005.04]: Artist File - Phillip Buehler (Box 121, Folder 3)
  - Traffic [2005.04]: Artist File - Shibetz Cohen (Box 121, Folder 4)
  - Traffic [2005.04]: Artist File - Yasushi Noguchi, 2004 (Box 121, Folder 5)
  - Traffic [2005.04]: Artist File - Providence Initiative for Psychogeographic Studies (PIPS) (Box 121, Folder 6)
  - Traffic [2005.04]: Artist File - Jenny Polak (Box 121, Folder 7)
  - Traffic [2005.04]: Artist File - Jonathan Allen (Box 121, Folder 8)
  - Traffic [2005.04]: Artist File - Justin Beal (Box 121, Folder 9)
  - Traffic [2005.04]: Artist File - Gail V. Biederman (Box 121, Folder 10)
  - Traffic [2005.04]: Artist File - Johannes Buss (Box 121, Folder 11)
  - Traffic [2005.04]: Artist File - Alfredo Conde (Box 121, Folder 12)
  - Traffic [2005.04]: Artist File - Matthew Cusick (Box 121, Folder 13)
  - Traffic [2005.04]: Artist File - Michel de Broin (Box 121, Folder 14)
  - Traffic [2005.04]: Artist File - Lisa DiLillo (Box 121, Folder 15)
  - Traffic [2005.04]: Artist File - Uri Dotan, September 22, 2005 (Box 121, Folder 16)
  - Traffic [2005.04]: Artist File - Hasan M. Elahi (Box 121, Folder 17)
  - Traffic [2005.04]: Artist File - eteam, August 19, 2005 (Box 121, Folder 18)
  - Traffic [2005.04]: Artist List - Eddie Figueroa, 2005 - 2006 (Box 121, Folder 19)
  - Traffic [2005.04]: Artist File - Chantal Foretich, 2005 - 2006 (Box 121, Folder 20)
  - Traffic [2005.04]: Artist File - Adam Frelin (Box 121, Folder 21)
  - Traffic [2005.04]: Artist File - Graciela Fuentes (Box 121, Folder 22)
  - Traffic [2005.04]: Artist File - Christoph Gielen (Box 121, Folder 23)
  - Traffic [2005.04]: Artist File - Eduardo Gil, August 24, 2005 (Box 121, Folder 24)
  - Traffic [2005.04]: Artist File - Shuli Hallak (Box 121, Folder 25)
  - Traffic [2005.04]: Artist File - Tom Hebert (Box 121, Folder 26)
  - Traffic [2005.04]: Artist File - Angela Hennessy (Box 121, Folder 27)
  - Traffic [2005.04]: Artist File - Todd Jokl (Box 121, Folder 28)
  - Traffic [2005.04]: Artist File - Marie-Christine Katz (Box 121, Folder 29)
  - Traffic [2005.04]: Artist File - Michael Lalicki, April 12, 2005 (Box 121, Folder 30)
  - Traffic [2005.04]: Artist File - Matthew Lusk, September 27, 2005 (Box 121, Folder 31)
  - Traffic [2005.04]: Artist File - Mitchell Marco, undated (Box 121, Folder 32)
  - Traffic [2005.04]: Artist File - Bryan Mesenbourg, September 14, 2005 (Box 131, Folder 33)
  - Traffic [2005.04]: Artist File - David Packer (Box 121, Folder 34)
  - Traffic [2005.04]: Artist File - Debra Pearlman (Box 122, Folder 1)
  - Traffic [2005.04]: Artist File - Plamen Petkov (Box 122, Folder 2)
  - Traffic [2005.04]: Artist File - Preemptive Media (Box 122, Folder 3)
  - Traffic [2005.04]: Artist File - Jeremy J. Quinn / Rise Industries (Box 122, Folder 4)
  - Traffic [2005.04]: Artist File - Nicholas Rodrigues (Box 122, Folder 5)
  - Traffic [2005.04]: Artist File - Augustine Romero (Box 122, Folder 6)
  - Traffic [2005.04]: Artist File - Shane Ruth (Box 122, Folder 7)
  - Traffic [2005.04]: Artist File - Zoe Sheehan Saldana (Box 122, Folder 8)
  - Traffic [2005.04]: Artist File - Marie P. Sauvaitre (Box 122, Folder 9)
  - Traffic [2005.04]: Artist File - Simon Schiessel and Saoirse Higgins (Box 122, Folder 10)
  - Traffic [2005.04]: Artist File - Romy Scheroder (Box 122, Folder 11)
  - Traffic [2005.04]: Artist File - Paul Slocum (Box 122, Folder 12)
  - Traffic [2005.04]: Artist File - Shannon Spanhake (Box 122, Folder 13)
  - Traffic [2005.04]: Artist File - Janos Sugar (Box 122, Folder 14)
  - Traffic [2005.04]: Artist File - Stefanie Trojan (Box 122, Folder 15)
  - Traffic [2005.04]: Artist File - Jovan Villalba (Box 122, Folder 16)
  - Traffic [2005.04]: Artist File - Lance Wakeling (Box 122, Folder 17)
  - Traffic [2005.04]: Artist File - Seth Weiner (Box 122, Folder 18)
  - Traffic [2005.04]: Artist File - Letha Wilson (Box 122, Folder 19)
  - Traffic [2005.04]: Artist File - Bradley Wood (Box 122, Folder 20)
  - Traffic [2005.04]: Artist File - Mike Wsol (Box 122, Folder 21)
  - Traffic [2005.04]: Artist File - Linda Wysong (Box 122, Folder 22)
  - World War 3 Illustrated [2005.05]: Administrative, Promotional (Box 122, Folder 23)
  - Holiday Windows [2005.06]: Invitations, October - November 2005 (Box 122, Folder 24)
  - Holiday Windows [2005.06]: Press Release, November 19, 2005 (Box 122, Folder 25)
  - Holiday Windows [2005.06]: Correspondence, October - November 2005 (Box 122, Folder 26)
  - Holiday Windows [2005.06]: Installation Notes and Clipping, 2000; 2005 (Box 122, Folder 27)
  - Holiday Windows [2005.06]: Artist File - Timothy Blum, October 27, 2005 (Box 122, Folder 28)
  - Holiday Windows [2005.06]: Artist File - Kate Gilmore and Ana Spurgen, October - November 2005 (Box 122, Folder 29)
  - Holiday Windows [2005.06]: Artist File - Charles Juhaz-Alvarado, October - November 2005 (Box 122, Folder 30)
  - Holiday Windows [2005.06]: Artist File - Jose Letelier and Jimmie Stone, 2005 - 2006 (Box 122, Folder 31)
  - Holiday Windows [2005.06]: Artist File - nicoykatiushka, 2005 - 2006 (Box 122, Folder 32)
  - Holiday Windows [2005.06]: Artist File - Seth Weiner, October - November 2005 (Box 123, Folder 1)
  - Holiday Windows [2005.06]: Artist File - Saya Woolfalk, 2005 - 2006 (Box 123, Folder 2)
  - The Studio Visit [2006.01]: Research, September 2005 (Box 123, Folder 3)
  - The Studio Visit [2006.01]: Reply Card Responses, 2005 (Box 123, Folder 4)
  - The Studio Visit [2006.01]: Invitations, 2005 - 2006 (Box 123, Folder 5)
  - The Studio Visit [2006.01]: Press Kit Materials (Box 123, Folder 6)
  - The Studio Visit [2006.01]: Release Forms, January - February 2006 (Box 123, Folder 7)
  - The Studio Visit [2006.01]: [Administrative Folders, Empty with Notation], undated (Box 123, Folder 8)
  - The Studio Visit [2006.01]: Exhibition Labels, undated (Box 123, Folder 9)
  - The Studio Visit [2006.01]: Correspondence - Artists' Spelling, 2005 - 2006 (Box 123, Folder 10)
  - The Studio Visit [2006.01]: Artists, A - D, 2005 - 2006 (Box 123, Folder 11)
  - The Studio Visit [2006.01]: Artists, E - H, 2005 - 2006 (Box 123, Folder 12)
  - The Studio Visit [2006.01]: Artists, I - K, 2005 - 2006 (Box 123, Folder 13)
  - The Studio Visit [2006.01]: Artists, L - P, 2005 - 2006 (Box 123, Folder 14)
  - The Studio Visit [2006.01]: Artists, Q - T, 2005 - 2006 (Box 123, Folder 15)
  - The Studio Visit [2006.01]: Artists, U - Z, 2005 - 2006 (Box 124, Folder 1)
  - The Studio Visit [2006.01]: Artist File - Chris Clary, 2005 - 2006 (Box 124, Folder 2)
  - The Studio Visit [2006.01]: Artist File - Aaron Kratch, 2005 - 2006 (Box 124, Folder 3)
  - The Studio Visit [2006.01]: Artist File - Cynthia von Buhler, 2004 - 2006 (Box 124, Folder 4)
  - The Studio Visit [2006.01]: Artist File - Paul Wirhun (Eggman), 2005 - 2006 (Box 124, Folder 5)
  - The Studio Visit [2006.01]: Window Proposals, 2005 (Box 124, Folder 6)
  - The Studio Visit [2006.01]: Artists' Resumes, Work Descriptions (Box 124, Folder 7)
  - The Studio Visit [2006.01]: Night Events (Box 124, Folder 8)
  - The Drop [2006.02]: Invitations, 2005 - 2006 (Box 124, Folder 9)
  - The Drop [2006.02]: Call For Proposals, Reject Letter, Conditions, February 2006 (Box 124, Folder 10)
  - The Drop [2006.02]: Shipping, Installation Instructions, Narratives, undated (Box 124, Folder 11)
  - The Drop [2006.02]: Exhibition Checklists, undated (Box 124, Folder 12)
  - The Drop [2006.02]: Correspondence, 2005 - 2006 (Box 124, Folder 13)
  - The Drop [2006.02]: Funding, 2004; 2006 (Box 124, Folder 14)
  - The Drop [2006.02]: Press Release, Publicity (Box 124, Folder 15)
  - The Drop [2006.02]: Loan and Release Forms (Box 124, Folder 16)
  - The Drop [2006.02]: Public Programs, 2005 - 2006 (Box 124, Folder 17)
  - The Drop [2006.02]: Artist File - Artists Formerly Known As Women (Box 124, Folder 18)
  - The Drop [2006.02]: Artist File - Lillian Ball, 2005 - 2006 (Box 124, Folder 19)
  - The Drop [2006.02]: Artist File - Justin Beal (Box 124, Folder 20)
  - The Drop [2006.02]: Artist File - Brandon Ballengee (Box 124, Folder 21)
  - The Drop [2006.02]: Artist File - Bob Braine, 2005, 2006 (Box 124, Folder 22)
  - The Drop [2006.02]: Artist File - Donna Conlon, 2005, 2006 (Box 124, Folder 23)
  - The Drop [2006.02]: Artist File - Nancy Drew (Box 125, Folder 1)
  - The Drop [2006.02]: Artist File - Catherine M. Forster (Box 125, Folder 2)
  - The Drop [2006.02]: Artist File - Peter Fend (Box 125, Folder 3)
  - The Drop [2006.02]: Artist File - Adam Frelin, February 14, 2006 (Box 125, Folder 4)
  - The Drop [2006.02]: Artist File - Basia Irland, 2005, 2006 (Box 125, Folder 5)
  - The Drop [2006.02]: Artist File - Sant Khalsa, 2005, 2006 (Box 125, Folder 6)
  - The Drop [2006.02]: Artist File - Eve Andree Laramee, 2005, 2006 (Box 125, Folder 7)
  - The Drop [2006.02]: Artist File - Cynthia Lawson Jaramillo (Box 125, Folder 8)
  - The Drop [2006.02]: Artist File - Amy Lipton (Box 125, Folder 9)
  - The Drop [2006.02]: Artist File - Lucia Pizzani (Box 125, Folder 10)
  - The Drop [2006.02]: Artist File - Andrea Polli (Box 125, Folder 11)
  - The Drop [2006.02]: Artist File - Aviva Rahmani (Box 125, Folder 12)
  - The Drop [2006.02]: Artist File - Ann Rosenthal (Box 125, Folder 13)
  - The Drop [2006.02]: Artist File - Christy Rupp (Box 125, Folder 14)
  - The Drop [2006.02]: Artist File - Fidel Sclavo (Box 125, Folder 15)
  - The Drop [2006.02]: Artist File - Alan Sonfist, 2005 (Box 125, Folder 16)
  - The Drop [2006.02]: Artist File - Arbuzo Virtmanis (Box 125, Folder 17)
  - The Drop [2006.02]: Artist File - Harlan D. Whatley (Box 125, Folder 18)
  - The Drop [2006.02]: Artist File - Bryan Zanisnik (Box 125, Folder 19)
  - The Drop [2006.02]: Research - Tropical Area, 2005 (Box 125, Folder 20)
  - The Drop [2006.02]: Research - Exhibitions [1 of 2], 2002, 2004 (Box 125, Folder 21)
  - The Drop [2006.02]: Research - Exhibitions [2 of 2], 2004 - 2006 (Box 126, Folder 1)
  - The Drop [2006.02]: Research - Environmental Organizations, 1998, 2001 - 2006 (Box 126, Folder 2)
  - The Drop [2006.02]: Research - Potential Artists, 2005 - 2006 (Box 126, Folder 3)
  - The Drop [2006.02]: Research - Pollution, Policy, 1985, 2004 - 2006 (Box 126, Folder 4)
  - The Drop [2006.02]: Research - Clippings from Literature, 2001 - 2004 (Box 126, Folder 5)
  - The Drop [2006.02]: Research - Clippings from Periodicals [1 of 2], 2000, 2004 (Box 126, Folder 6)
  - The Drop [2006.02]: Research - Clippings from Periodicals [2 of 2], 2000 - 2005 (Box 127, Folder 1)
  - Wild Girls [2006.03]: Invitations, Programs, June - August 2006 (Box 127, Folder 2)
  - Wild Girls [2006.03]: Press Release, Publicity, June - August 2006 (Box 127, Folder 3)
  - Wild Girls [2006.03]: Checklists, undated (Box 127, Folder 4)
  - Wild Girls [2006.03]: Press Plan, Correspondence (Box 127, Folder 5)
  - Wild Girls [2006.03]: Curatorial Meeting Minutes, June 2006 (Box 127, Folder 6)
  - Wild Girls [2006.03]: Wall Labels, undated (Box 127, Folder 7)
  - Wild Girls [2006.03]: Public Programs - Performance Series, July - August 2006 (Box 127, Folder 8)
  - Wild Girls [2006.03]: Loan Forms, June 2006 (Box 127, Folder 9)
  - Wild Girls [2006.03]: Shipping Invoices, June - September 2006 (Box 127, Folder 10)
  - Wild Girls [2006.03]: Condition Reports, August 2006 (Box 127, Folder 11)
  - Wild Girls [2006.03]: Research (Box 127, Folder 12)
  - Wild Girls [2006.03]: Artist File - Alia Farid Abdal, June 19, 2006 (Box 127, Folder 13)
  - Wild Girls [2006.03]: Artist File - Jaishri Abichandani, June 2006 (Box 127, Folder 14)
  - Wild Girls [2006.03]: Artist File - Francisca Benitez, undated (Box 127, Folder 15)
  - Wild Girls [2006.03]: Artist File - Ogechi Chieke, undated (Box 127, Folder 16)
  - Wild Girls [2006.03]: Artist File - Katia Damianova, undated (Box 127, Folder 17)
  - Wild Girls [2006.03]: Artist File - Taylor Davis, June 2006 (Box 127, Folder 18)
  - Wild Girls [2006.03]: Artist File - Georganne Deen, June 2006 (Box 127, Folder 19)
  - Wild Girls [2006.03]: Artist File - Jenny Dubnau, June 2006 (Box 127, Folder 20)
  - Wild Girls [2006.03]: Artist File - Chitra Ganesh (Box 127, Folder 21)
  - Wild Girls [2006.03]: Artist File - Alla Georgieva, June 2006 (Box 127, Folder 22)
  - Wild Girls [2006.03]: Artist File - Kate Gilmore, June 15, 2006 (Box 127, Folder 23)
  - Wild Girls [2006.03]: Artist File - Vlatka Horvat, 2006, 2007 (Box 127, Folder 24)
  - Wild Girls [2006.03]: Artist File - Katalina Hurralde, May 2006 (Box 127, Folder 25)
  - Wild Girls [2006.03]: Artist File - Emily Keown, May - June 2006 (Box 127, Folder 26)
  - Wild Girls [2006.03]: Artist File - Saeri Kitrani (Box 127, Folder 27)
  - Wild Girls [2006.03]: Artist File - Tamara Kostianovsky, 2003, 2006 (Box 127, Folder 28)
  - Wild Girls [2006.03]: Artist File - Katarzyna Kozyra, June 21, 2006 (Box 127, Folder 29)
  - Wild Girls [2006.03]: Artist File - Simone Lee, June - July 2006 (Box 127, Folder 30)
  - Wild Girls [2006.03]: Artist File - Jennifer Levonian, May 2006 (Box 127, Folder 31)
  - Wild Girls [2006.03]: Artist File - nicoykatiushka (Box 127, Folder 32)
  - Wild Girls [2006.03]: Artist File - Wanda Ortiz, undated (Box 127, Folder 33)
  - Wild Girls [2006.03]: Artist File - Maria Eugenia Piñeres, June 2006 (Box 128, Folder 1)
  - Wild Girls [2006.03]: Artist File - Ana Rose Rivera, May - June 2006 (Box 128, Folder 2)